Listen to me carefully, everyone. During this mission, I won't tolerate any failures. Follow my orders to the letter and don't fool around. This mission will probably be the most dangerous you will ever have. Many of you will die.
Remember, everyone here is family. That means those who fall in battle are our brothers and sisters. But they won't die in vain. Their sacrifices will ensure our success. Let me be clear. Our goal isn't to come back alive. It is to be victorious no matter what. Do you understand?
Shinoa, how much longer?
We've got about 20 minutes.
Everyone, fall in line.
I want to go over our plan of attack again.
We began at 1400 hours.
Our gathered troops will move in teams, attacking in unison.
If all goes as planned, eight targets will be executed, leaving two nobles alive.
Our target's a strong one, Lukul Wesker, the 15th progenitor.
We plan to engage him here.
If we're unable to take him by surprise, our priority is to cut off his retreat and prevent
him from joining the other nobles.
Once our target is dead, we'll hold off any remaining vampires until the Lieutenant Colonel
supplies us with new orders.
In this case scenario, all the targets are killed simultaneously, and we don't have a problem
regrouping and killing the remaining two nobles in Nagoya.
If the targets aren't destroyed and the nobles join forces, there's no way we'll be able
to beat them.
All of our targets are located fairly close to one another, but since our assembled forces
have been split into small groups, it should keep the targets busy.
Our team's one of the smallest.
That means there must be high expectations for us.
Even though there aren't as many troops in our squad, failure is not an option.
If you make a mistake, it'll affect the lives of all 100 of your comrades.
You have to remember that.
We will.
Ah, right, so basically all we gotta do is kill this Lululala guy, right?
No sweat.
Come on, man.
Fooling around will get us killed.
This is behind enemy lines.
Have you forgotten what the Lieutenant Colonel said?
Huh?
I'm just saying that it's not gonna be that hard.
Show some respect.
This kid.
He isn't serious.
Sergeant Narami, can't we be reassigned?
There's no way I can trust these kids to have my back.
Whoa, calm down, Rika.
We have to work alongside them.
We don't really have time to switch out.
This kind of unrest isn't good.
They hate us.
Go apologize.
Um, I apologize, Sergeant Narami.
I'll make sure my squad is ready to follow order.
I don't need anyone to apologize.
Just remember, we need to be on our toes.
If one person drags us down, then we're all as good as dead.
I don't want to lose a comrade because of a single screw-up.
What is it?
Do you not agree with what I said?
No.
I mean, yes.
What I'm saying is that I feel the same way.
I don't want to lose any comrades either.
I don't need excuses.
I need you to act-
Listen!
Our squads, we're in this together, so I'll make sure that none of us get hurt.
Then the least you can do is remember our target's name.
There's more to being a good soldier than the ability to swing a sword.
There's no point in remembering the name of someone you're just going to kill.
But, I do remember the names of the people I'm going to protect.
Got it?
Shinoa, Kimizuki, Mitsuba, Yoichi, Makoto Narumi, Yayoi Endo, Rika Inoue, Taro Kageyama, Shusaku Iwasuki.
I won't let my comrades get killed.
We'll show Gorin we can be victorious without losing a single teammate.
I apologize if my subordinate's attitude is out of line, Sergeant Narumi.
But, everyone on my squad feels the same.
We're with you 100%.
We may be noobs, but we'll follow our directives and try our best not to drag anyone down.
I swear this on my honor and my life.
Fine, then.
The mission will begin in six minutes.
Yayoi, report.
Our target should be in sight soon.
Any second, according to our intelligence.
He visits the park around this time every day without fail.
This sounded like a good idea in theory, but now that it's time I'm getting kinda nervous.
Keep it together.
We've got the upper hand today.
We're taking them completely by surprise.
Let's do this together.
Without any deaths, no one hurt.
A victorious mission with all targets executed.
Got it.
We should get started.
What's wrong, Yoichi?
You're starting to make me nervous.
We've still got five minutes before the mission begins.
Yeah, I know.
But what happens if we screw up and the whole thing turns...
Don't even entertain the idea.
With any luck, we'll finish him off.
Then we'll be war heroes.
Worry too much, and you'll mess up for sure.
Now then.
This is your first sniper mission, right?
What's wrong, Yoichi?
You're starting to make me nervous.
We've still got five minutes before the mission begins.
Yeah, I know.
But what happens if we screw up and the whole thing turns...
Don't even entertain the idea.
With any luck, we'll finish him off.
Then we'll be war heroes.
Worry too much, and you'll mess up for sure.
Now then.
This is your first sniper mission, right?
Gurren asked me to teach you a few things to get you prepared.
Like I said, first you need to calm down.
Okay.
Great.
Try to take it easy, and remember that we're not alone.
If we don't take Wesker down, then the others will.
That's all.
Then the others will.
That's the whole reason the close combat team exists anyway.
Right.
Snipers need to keep their cool.
It's the only way we're gonna pick off enemies, and back up our comrades.
Or kill them if they're captured, saving them from unspeakable torture at the hands of the vampires.
You'd kill your own teammates?
If necessary, yeah.
But as long as we land our shots, we won't have to worry about anything like that.
So unwind.
Take a deep breath.
Alright.
Relax your muscles.
Focus on trying to slow down your pulse.
Once you're breathing steadily, try calling for your demon.
Come out, Gekko-een.
Thank you for that.
I feel better.
Good boy.
Stay alert.
Our target should show himself any time now.
Go ahead and get the park in your sights.
Okay.
There are lots of normal vampires walking around down there.
Ignore them.
Focus on finding that noble.
Right.
Here he comes.
He's the one in the hat.
That's Lukul Wesker.
Don't get an itchy trigger finger.
Wait until I give you the signal.
Otherwise, all our plans will be thrown off.
Got it.
Hmm.
Not bad today.
Where's it from?
This was collected in Naka.
Prisoner 58.
Female.
Age 4.
Hmm.
I do love the mellow taste of frightened young girls.
I insist that you have a sip, Esther.
Thank you.
But I've already had more than my share to drink today thanks to your generosity, my lord.
But this is a rare treat.
Blood of the highest quality.
Perfection.
It should be savored while it's fresh.
Please, enjoy yourself.
I'll try it once we've returned to the compound.
Very well.
Now, business.
What do you make of the absurd letter I received from cruel Tepish?
I assume that you are referring to her plan to annihilate the Japanese Imperial Demon Army?
The arrogance of that woman handing out orders from her fragile throne in Kyoto, insisting that we deal with a few insignificant humans.
I don't like it.
Since when do I follow her commands?
We are affiliated with a different political party.
There's no need for us to act until we've received orders straight from the Progenitor Council.
Hmm.
Although, rumor has it Queen Krul is coming to Nagoya to oversee things herself.
Oh, is that right?
Yes.
Hmm.
Then perhaps it would be wise to comply.
Difficult to say.
Last I heard, your actual boss, Lest Carr, was still engaged in a power struggle with Krul.
Meaning I'll be punished if I help her.
Well, I suppose the only thing to do...
Hmm?
Lord Luko...
Everyone take your cursed stimulant pills now!
It's time.
Let's make this quick.
How unfortunate.
My sword.
Drink of my blood.
We missed!
Don't fall apart yet.
Take down as many vampires as you can before jumping to safety.
Yeah, okay.
Narumi.
Let me take the first strike.
I'll gauge the enemy's strength.
Just cover me!
You've got my permission.
Make it count!
Nice shooting, Yoichi.
The livestock are attacking.
How pathetic.
Call it.
Call us whatever you want.
I'll show you who's really pathetic.
They have a plan to help I walk out.
I'll gauge the enemy's strength.
Follow me on Monday.
I've got the commander in theожет mail.
Ok, so it's more utilizar uhm...
The livestock are attacking. How pathetic.
Call us whatever you want. I'll show you who's really pathetic.
I have to admit, I can't wait to take your head.
You're finished!
Don't fool yourself, human.
This is checkmate.
Out of the way!
Such a weakling. You were my target from the beginning.
Crap!
That's it! Die, bloodsuckers!
I don't think so. Human.
Now, Shizuku!
Hurry up and do it!
Aka Heavy. Now bring in this vampire skull.
Nice! Good work, team! This is it!
Overestimating yourselves as usual.
Cover his escape!
We can't let him join up with the other nobles.
Everyone maintain the formation.
Stick to our strategy and we'll take him as a unit.
Interesting.
You lot must be the humans that Cruel Tepish is so annoyed by lately.
You don't seem so tough.
We attack together.
Hold up.
We can't keep this formation and stop him from escaping.
We need to lure him in close enough to surround him.
That sounds a lot easier than it actually is.
Unless you've got a plan.
What the hell are you doing?
Please, you can trust them to handle this.
Hey, ugly bloodsucker.
You bastards can reattach your arms, but can you grow a brand new one?
Why don't we find out?
You're making a mistake, human.
You don't want to make me angry.
It's your dominant arm, right?
Well, if you want it, you better start begging.
I'll kill you.
Huh?
What'd you just say?
That a fancy vampire noble can't beat a couple of humans?
Insufferable livestock.
I'll kill every one of you!
Look, shark!
This is it!
Die!
The only one dying today is you!
Are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Real!
Damn.
Pathetic humans.
Yayoi!
Finish him!
Right!
I refuse to be killed by livestock.
Yayoi!
you did it you nice job hey don't forget I promoted yeah you're really good at annoying
people yeah hey yo ichi thanks for the backup we couldn't have done it without you she knew
taught me how to be a much better sniper this proves it working together we really can destroy
the nobles I wonder if the other squads are
doing okay
this means you've beaten us we will destroy you shut up
damn that was too close lieutenant colonel
everything's fine this went just as planned really because we almost just got our butts handed to us
even though we're the strongest team you should have given us some backup think about it if we
struggled this much then it was definitely the right move to increase the manpower for all the
other teams yeah but none of that really matters if our commander gets killed and that's why I left
Shinya above ground if I die in battle then he'll step forward to lead lieutenant colonel Gurren
Kusanoki what happened to you
Kusanoki I'm afraid you're not going to make it please report for your comrades while you can
what happened sir I'm sorry but we failed to kill our target our 45 member squad
they've been wiped out the vampires want you to go to city hall they asked for you specifically
you have to why should I obey them they killed 19 of our men but the rest are being held hostage
they're all still alive please forgive us it's all right it wasn't your fault this was my mission
so the blame's on me you can relax now goshi I'm already on it
you'll sleep now lieutenant colonel sir it's been such an honor to fight for you
to serve thank you
rest you can watch us defeat these bastards from heaven you poor idiot
let me be the first to say it this is clearly some kind of trap
we'd be fools to go that said we're still going aren't we
we'll join with Narumi and Haragi squad
our target is the 13th progenitor his name is Crowley Eusford
um
you
Mm.
Next time on Seraph of the End, Sword of Justice.